# BUNANGO MOSES JOHN

Dar es Salaam | +255 675 805 660 | bunangomoses@gmail.com

# **OBJECTIVE**

Third-year computer engineering and IT student at the University of Dar es Salaam, with some experience in software development and programming, analytical and problem-solving skills, and a passion for technology and innovation where I can utilize the knowledge, I have gained in software development, programming, and problem-solving techniques to deal with challenges facing the community.

# **Skills Summary**

- Basic computer skills (familiarity with Microsoft Office Suite and Google Suite)
- Programing skills in Java and C programing language.
- Skills in flutter and laravel frameworks.
- Good communication skills (fluent in English and Kiswahili)

## Education

## November 2020 - Present

Currently a Third Year Student, BSc. Computer Engineering and IT, University of Dar es Salaam.

## 2018-2020

Advanced Level Education, Nsumba boys High School, Mwanza, Tanzania. Major: PCM (Physics, Chemistry and Mathematics).

## 2014-2017

Ordinary Level Education, St. Peter Claver High Secondary School (SPCHS), Dodoma, Tanzania.

#### 2007-2013

Primary School, Upendo English Medium Primary School, Mwanza, Tanzania.

# Experience

#### MWANZA CITY COUNCIL

Intern Hardware and Software Maintenance personnel | July 2021 - September 2021

• Installation of GoTHOMIS health system in most of district dispensaries and hospitals to enable intranet within those specific organizations i.e. dispensaries and hospital

- Worked as a software maintenance personnel for all the systems at the organization.
- Network management at the organization

# Oval Technologies, HQ

Internship | February 2022 - March 2022

• Worked as a Full stack web and Mobile app developer, specifically in flutter and largel frameworks.

# Oval Technologies, HQ

Intern Digital Channels Systems Personnel | July 2022 - September 2022

• Worked as a Full stack web developer, participated in Smart Mauzo e-commerce web. Specifically using Laravel framework.

# **Additional Information**

• Member at the Youth for Children (Y4C) hub At the University of Dar es salaam.

## Referees

Oval Technologies MD | +2554350846